<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Find Your First Linux Distro</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="text_intro">Welcome to Find Your First Linux Distro!
        That old PC still has value.
        This app helps you select your first Linux distro based on the specs of 
        your PC.  On the next page, answer the questions shown, and then click on 
        the Submit button to see the recommended solution. 
    </string>
    <string name="question_purpose">
        1.  Are you trying to rescue files from a hard drive that does not boot up,
        or are you ready to install a new OS?
    </string>
    
    <string-array name="purpose_array">
        <item>Rescuing files from a hard drive</item>
        <item>Ready to install a new OS</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="question_age">
        2.  When was your PC built or purchased by the original owner?
    </string>
    
    <string-array name="age_array">
        <item>Windows Vista era or later</item>
        <item>Windows XP era</item>
        <item>Windows 98/ME/2000 era</item>
        <item>Windows 95 era or earlier</item>
    </string-array>

   	<string name="question_memory">
        3.  How much memory does your computer have?
    </string>
    
   	<string-array name="memory_array">
        <item>At least 2 GB</item>
        <item>At least 512 MB</item>
        <item>At least 128 MB</item>
        <item>Under 128 MB</item>
    </string-array>
    
   	<string name="solution_puppy">
   	    Your purpose: rescuing files from a hard drive
   	    \nAge of your computer: Windows 98 era or newer
   	    \nComputer memory: at least 128 MB
   	    \n\nRecommended Linux distro: Puppy Linux
   	    \n\nA Puppy Linux CD is an excellent tool for rescuing files from your hard
   	    drive.  Puppy Linux is exceptionally lightweight.  If you have at least 256 
   	    MB of memory, it loads into RAM and is exceptionally quick.  The unique 
   	    run-as-root feature is very convenient for copying files from the internal 
   	    drive to an external drive.
   	</string>
   	<string name="solution_tinycore">
   	    Your purpose: rescuing files from a hard drive
   	    \n\nRecommended Linux distro: TinyCore Linux?
   	    \n\nYour computer cannot run Puppy Linux because it is too old (Windows 95
   	    era) or has insufficient memory (under 128 MB).  One solution is to boot up
   	    with TinyCore Linux, which has an ISO size of only 10 MB.  Another solution
   	    is to use a special adapter that allows you to convert your old internal
   	    hard drive into an external hard drive that you can connect to the USB port
   	    of a newer computer that can run Puppy Linux.
   	</string>
   	<string name="solution_mint_ubuntu">
   	    Your purpose: installation on a hard drive
   	    \nAge of your computer: Windows Vista era or newer
   	    \nComputer memory: at least 2 GB
   	    \n\nRecommended Linux distro: Linux Mint Main Edition
   	    \n\nGiven that your computer is only a few years old and is fast enough for
   	    Windows Vista/7/8, your best bet is Linux Mint Main Edition (based on
   	    Ubuntu Linux).  Linux Mint is the most popular Linux distro and is 
   	    well-known for user-friendliness and a large community.  Of all editions 
   	    available for Linux Mint, the Main Edition is the most widely used, and 
   	    that means better support and a larger pool of fellow users who can 
   	    answer your questions.
   	</string>
   	<string name="solution_mint_debian">
   	    Your purpose: installation on a hard drive
   	    \nAge of your computer: Windows XP era or newer
   	    \nComputer memory: at least 512 MB
   	    \n\nRecommended Linux distro: Linux Mint Debian Edition
   	    \n\nGiven that your computer is several years old and is fast enough for
   	    Windows XP but not Windows Vista/7/8, Linux Mint Debian Edition is your 
   	    best bet.  LMDE offers the user-friendliness and smoothness of the 
   	    traditional Ubuntu-based editions of Linux Mint but bypasses the heavy
   	    Ubuntu overhead in order to provide lighter and faster operation.  
   	</string>
   	<string name="solution_antix">
   	    Your purpose: installation on a hard drive
   	    \nAge of your computer: Windows 98 era or newer
   	    \nComputer memory: at least 128 MB
   	    \n\nRecommended Linux distro: antiX Linux
   	    \n\nGiven that your computer is ancient but still fast enough for Windows 
   	    98, your best bet is antiX Linux, the lightweight derivative of MEPIS 
   	    Linux.  The full version of antiX Linux is very fast and lightweight, yet 
   	    is also user-friendly.  Unlike other lightweight Linux distros, 
   	    antiX Linux is fully compatible with the Debian software repository and
   	    thus gives you access to over 30,000 software packages.  
   	</string>
   	<string name="solution_museum">
   	    Your purpose: installation on a hard drive
   	    \nRecommended Linux distro: none   	    
   	    \n\nYour computer is too old or has insufficient memory for running the
   	    full version of antiX Linux.  Unless you are geeky enough to use a distro 
   	    that requires substantial tweaking, your computer is too obsolete for
   	    everyday use.  It is probably time to donate your computer to a museum 
   	    exhibit.
   	</string>
   	
        
</resources>